(
"ai_sub_version": "1.12.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "h264_qsv"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
新衣装お披露目＆超告知あり！？
Sakura Miko Birthday Live 2026 Fashion Beat
New Outfit Reveal & Super Announcement!?
さくらみこ
Sakura Miko
大空スバル / 常闇トワ
Oozora Subaru / Tokoyami Towa
白上フブキ / 大神ミオ
Shirakami Fubuki / Ookami Mio
宝鐘マリン / 戌神ころね / 百鬼あやめ
Houshou Marine / Inugami Korone / Nakiri Ayame
Sakura Miko Birthday Live 2026
Fashion Beat
DAIDAIDAIファンタジスタ
作詞・作曲・編曲：ヒゲドライバー
DAIDAIDAI Fantasista
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Hige Driver
ニャッホー！ハロー！！
Nya! Hello!!
The beautiful days!!
刮目してくれ！
Keep your eyes on me!
Please call “Elite”!!
(Funky dancin baby! ah)
(Ah!)
さあ、お待たせしました！
Now, sorry to keep you waiting!
始めちゃえ！
Let's get started!
今日も引き締めて
Get focused again today
いざ、挑戦だ！
Now, it's a challenge!
躊躇は厳禁
Hesitation is strictly forbidden
足踏みしてないで
Don't just stand there tapping your feet
一緒にせーので
Together on "one, two..."
もっと前にいこう
Let's go further forward
ね？
Right?
さあ、なんとかなっちゃえ！
Now, let it work out somehow!
飛び込んで
Jump in
なんたってじっとしてても
Because even if you stay still
人生は冒険だ
Life is an adventure
こんがらがったら
If you get all tangled up
またわかんないぞ
You won't know what's what again
道のりはこんなんだ
The path is just like this
なんなんだ！
What's going on!
全力だ！
Go all out!
あはは！
Ahaha!
みとめ、みとめちゃって
Admit, just admit it
気持ちにまかせちゃって
Just leave it to your feelings
あれ、いったいぜんたいどうしたん？
Wait, what on earth happened?
絶体絶命
A desperate situation
君たちには
For you guys
涙は似合わないね！
Tears don't suit you!
ダダダダ大冒険に
To the big, big, big, big adventure
飛び出そうぜ！
Let's leap out!
いざ、ダダダダ大心配も
Now, even the big, big, big, big worries
重ねて
Pile them up
成長して
And grow
Happy! I feel so...
君と笑い話にしよう
Let's make them into a funny story with you
（うえい！）
(Uei!)
ダダダダ大問題も
Even the big, big, big, big problems
吹き飛ばせ！
Blow them away!
いつかダダダダ大団円の
Someday, the big, big, big, big grand finale
素敵な結末へ
To a wonderful conclusion
Please me!!
さぁ、ついてきて！
Now, follow me!
進め！前代未聞の
Advance! Into the unprecedented
New world!
Let's go!!
あながち間違ってる
Not necessarily wrong
また墓穴も掘ってる
Digging another grave too
勉強、勉強！
Study, study!
はいはいはい、知ってます。待って、なんか言ってる！！
Yeah yeah yeah, I know. Wait, they're saying something!!
ぶっちゃけ、有識者の
To be honest, to all the experts
皆様に感謝してます！
I'm grateful to you all!
Nice comments 待ってんぜ
I'm waiting for your nice comments
（あ～ね！）
(Aa-ne!)
うじうじしちゃって
Dithering and dallying
心にノックしちゃって
Knocking on your heart
ほら、だんだんだんだん倒しちゃえ
Look, knock them down one by one
絶体絶命
A desperate situation
僕たちには
For us
笑顔が足りてないね！
We don't have enough smiles!
ダダダダ大好きだ済ませない
I won't end with just "I love you"
いざ、ダダダダ満足の
Now, for the big, big, big, big satisfaction
その上の感動を
And the emotion beyond that
もっと欲しがっちゃって
Wanting even more
五感に贅沢にいこう
Let's be extravagant for our five senses
（うえい！）
(Uei!)
全全全然なってないって
You're not there yet, not at all
へこんじゃったって
Even if you're feeling down
ならば前進前進エンジンの
Then, move forward, forward, with the engine's
本気のマジの全力で
Serious, true, full power
ニャッホー！
Nyaho!
The beautiful days!!
踏み込んで進め
Step in and advance
Freedom way!
(wow wow wow wow)
乗り遅れないようにね
Make sure you don't miss out
(wow wow wow wow)
声を聞かせてくれ Yeah!
Let me hear your voice, Yeah!
(wow wow wow wow)
歌は越えてはるかに
The song will reach far beyond
(wow wow wow wow)
ベイベー！ベイベー！ベイベー！
Baby! Baby! Baby!
なんていうか、あ、なんだかちょっと言わせない
How should I put it, ah, it's kind of hard to say
一人ぼっちで見てた光景を
今はきっとあなたと冒険してる！
The scenery I used to watch all alone
I'm surely adventuring through it with you now!
ダダダダダダダダ
Dadadada dadadada
ダダダダ大好きじゃ様ならない
I won't end with just "I love you"
だから！
So!
ダダダダ最高な
To the big, big, big, big greatest
メロディに乗せて全力で
Melody, moving at full power
ニャッホー！
Nyaho!
飛ばしちゃえ！
Let's blow it all away!
ずっと大冒険しよう
Let's adventure forever
イェイ！
Yay!
ダダダダ大問題も
Even the big, big, big, big problems
吹き飛ばせ！
Blow them away!
いつかダダダダ大団円の
Someday, the big, big, big, big grand finale
素敵な結末へ
To a wonderful conclusion
Please me!!
さぁ、ついてきて！
Now, follow me!
進め！前代未聞の
Advance! Into the unprecedented
New world!
刮目してくれ！
Keep your eyes on me!
Please call “Elite”!!
(Funky dancin baby! ah)
(Ah!)
100点満点中、100億点！！
Out of 100 points, 10 billion points!!
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" isn't enough
一番大事がいい
I want to be your number one
君がつくるオリジナルな特別
The original special something you create
特別チューして。
Make it a special kiss.
眩しくって、目が覚めて
So dazzling, I woke up
Oh yeah!
愛しく思ってよ
Think of me dearly
Oh yeah!
眠り姫のように
Like the Sleeping Beauty
優しく口づけて
Kiss me gently
ゴミめいた この世界
This trashy world
Oh yeah!
ピュアが架かる 君がいる
Where you are, pure light shines
Oh yeah!
全てに触れずに
Without touching everything
２人だけでいよう
Let's just be the two of us
私のこと 独占して
Monopolize me
君だけのモノになってもいい
I don't mind becoming yours alone
何でもある日の「何でもない」
The "nothing" of a day where there's everything
気付いてね
Please notice it
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough
君の「特別」にして
Make me your "special one"
ねえもっと Give me a kiss も 私は
Hey, more, give me a kiss, I'm
君でいっぱいよ
Full of you
ほどけない リボン結び
An unlooseable ribbon knot
小指キュンって縛って
Tie my pinky tight with a squeeze
そうよ 一生一緒がいいもん
That's right, I want to be together forever
とくぺちゅが欲しい
I want a special kiss
２人きり週末は
The weekend with just the two of us
Oh yeah!
奏でてよ ハーモニー
Play our harmony
Oh yeah!
流れ星見たら
If you see a shooting star
私を想ってほしい
I want you to think of me
あまあまな君なのに
Even though you're so sweet
Oh yeah!
広い街 吸い込まれ
Being swallowed by the big city
Oh yeah!
戦う姿に
In your fighting figure
大きい花丸だね
I'll give you a big flower mark
好きなところ、
The things I like,
優しいとこ。
the kind parts.
嫌いなとこも、
Even the things I dislike,
優しいとこ。
are the kind parts.
誰にもあげない
I won't give you to anyone
私だけ
Only for me
独り占め！
All to myself!
う〜んだって 今までの人と
Hmm, because with people up until now
同じはいらないんです
I don't want the same things
ねえもっと Give me more love
Hey, more, give me more love
私のため 生きてほしいんです
I want you to live for me
だからウサギと私は
So, like a rabbit, I
寂しくさせないで
Don't make me lonely
そんなんじゃ 束縛じゃないわ
That kind of thing isn't restraint
苦しいのが好き
I like the painful parts
ショートケーキ イチゴみたいに
Like the strawberry on a shortcake
座ってもいい？
Can I sit there?
赤く甘い恋だもん
Because it's a red and sweet love
誰かにあげた「大好き」も
Even the "I love you"s you gave to someone else
返してもらって 全部私に
Give them back and give them all to me
ちょーだい！もっと！
Give it to me! More!
君は神様が作る
You are a person like
奇跡のようなヒト
a miracle created by God
拗ねた顔も その寝顔も
Your sulky face and your sleeping face
守ってあげるね
I'll protect them
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough
君の「特別」にして
Make me your "special one"
ねえもっと Give me a kiss も 私は
Hey, more, give me a kiss, I'm
君でいっぱいよ
Full of you
ほどけない リボン結び
An unlooseable ribbon knot
小指キュンって縛って
Tie my pinky tight with a squeeze
ねえ baby 最初で最後の
Hey baby, make me your first
特別にしてね
and last special one
はーい！みんなー！にょはろー！
Yes! Everyone! Nyahallo!
エリートみこアイドルのさくらみこでーす！
I'm the elite miko idol, Sakura Miko!
さくらみこ生誕祭2026
Sakura Miko Birthday Festival 2026
「Fashion Beat」に来てくれてどうもありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to "Fashion Beat"!
いぇーい！
Yay!
今年でなんと、みこちゃん、１８.８歳になりました！
This year, surprisingly, Miko-chan turned 18.8 years old!
たぶん１８.８歳だよね？
It's probably 18.8, right?
はい、あの、０.１でね、刻んでいく系のVTuberですから
Yes, well, since I'm the type of VTuber who increments by 0.1
今年も１８.８歳になっちゃいましたー！わー！
I've turned 18.8 again this year! Wah!
そしてそして、今回のライブのテーマは
And and, the theme of this live is
「Fashion Beat」にちなんでですね、「Fashion」となっております。
in connection with "Fashion Beat", it's "Fashion".
いろんな演出が盛りだくさんなので、ぜひ楽しんでください。
There are many different productions, so please enjoy them.
じゃあね、ちょっとま、ファッションちなむんでみこちゃんもちょっとだけチェンジしちゃおうかな？
So, since it's about fashion, maybe Miko-chan should change just a little bit?
はい、上向いててくださーい。
Yes, please look up.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
はい！じゃらーん！
Yes! Ta-da!
ということで、クリスマスのね、ライブ...
So, the Christmas live...
それではね、
Anyway,
あまり披露しなかったこちらの...
this one that I haven't shown much...
キャストオフバージョンになっておりまーす！
is the Cast Off version!
こんな感じになってます、可愛いでしょ？
It looks like this, cute right?
ちょっとセクシーですけどね。
It's a bit sexy though.
はい。
Yes.
可愛い！
So cute!
はい、次の曲はこれで披露しようと思っておりまーす。
Yes, I'm thinking of performing the next song in this.
そして、えー、先ほどね、2曲お送りしましたが、
And, well, I just performed two songs,
どうでしたか？
how were they?
みこのオリ曲の『ダイダイ・ダイ・ファンタジスタ』と、
Miko's original song 'Daidai Dai Fantasista',
そして、みこの大好きなアイドルさんのいとくぼさんの『特別しては』
and Miko's favorite idol group Itokubo's 'Tokubetsu shite wa',
を披露させていただきました。
which I performed.
とっても可愛かったでしょう？
It was very cute, right?
きゅるん！
Kyurun!
はい！
Yes!
あ、そうだ、ステージもね、ちょっと見せたいんですけど、
Oh, that's right, I also want to show you the stage,
見てください！
look!
こちら、今回のテーマにちなんで作っていただきました！
This was made based on this time's theme!
ドレッサーとかね、
Like the dresser,
めちゃくちゃね、
it's really...
なんかこう、みこが小人になったみたいな感じですけど、
it feels like Miko has become a small person,
ね、とっても可愛くなっております！
right, it's become very cute!
そして、こちらのトルソーね、
And these torsos,
みこちゃんの歴代の衣装とかも少し飾ってあります。
even have some of Miko-chan's past outfits on display.
全部じゃないんですけどね。はい。
Not all of them, though. Yes.
えー、
Well,
最後にですね、たくさんの告知があったりとか、
and then, there will be lots of announcements,
新衣装のお披露目もございますので、
and a new outfit reveal as well,
ぜひ楽しんでもらえたらなと思っております！
so I hope you all enjoy it!
では！
Now!
早速ゲストパート行こうと思いますよ！
let's get right into the guest part!
よし、こうして...
Alright, like this...
それでは、この後も楽しんでね！
Well then, please enjoy what's coming next!
よし！
Alright!
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
歌：さくらみこ・戌神ころね
作詞・作曲：Yasutaka Nakata(Capsule)
Fashion Monster
Vocals: Sakura Miko, Inugami Korone
Lyrics/Comp: Yasutaka Nakata (Capsule)
おもしろいって言いたいのに
I want to say it's interesting, but
言えないなんてつまんないでしょ
not being able to say it is boring, isn't it?
おなじになっていい子でなんて
Being the same and being a good girl,
いたくないってキミもそうでしょ
you don't want to do that either, do you?
だれかの
Someone's
ルールに
rules,
しばられたくはないの
I don't want to be bound by them
わがまま
Selfish
ドキドキ
Heart pounding
このままでいたい
I want to stay like this
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
せまいこころのおりも
The cage of a narrow mind,
こわしてじゆうになりたいの
I want to break it and be free
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
五覚を研ぎ澄ませてキミのように
Sharpen your five senses, like you
吸い込まれてくらせん模様みたいに
Being sucked in, like a spiral pattern
I wanna be free
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
ただふつうにいきたいのに
I just want to live normally, but
へんなことってつまんないでしょ
being called weird is boring, isn't it?
きめつけないでいい子でなんて
Don't decide for me, being a good girl,
いたくないってキミもそうでしょ
you don't want to be like that either, do you?
だって
Because
ルールに
by the rules
縛られたくはないの
I don't want to be bound
わがまま
Selfish
ドキドキ
Heart-throbbing
このままでいたい
I want to stay like this
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
鉄の首飾りをはずして
Take off the iron necklace
ただ自由に行きたいだけ
I just want to live freely
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
この狭い心の檻も
Even this narrow cage of my heart
壊して自由になりたいの
I want to break it and be free
ファッションモンスター
Fashion Monster
咲き誇れ　花よ舞い踊れ
Bloom in full glory, flowers, dance on
明日を虹色に染め上げて
Dyeing tomorrow in rainbow colors
行くぞー！
Let's go!
ほっ！
Hoi!
はっ！
Ha!
ソイヤ！ソイヤ！ソイヤ！
Soiya! Soiya! Soiya!
はじまるよー！
It's starting!
今から歌うわ ウルトラスーパー
I'll sing from now on, ultra-super
糸とお菓子の 夢色リズム
Yumairo rhythm of strings and sweets
おかしなゆえにね 心惹かれるわ
I'm drawn to it because it's strange
もっともっと弾ませて どうでもいいの
Make it bounce more and more, it doesn't matter
大事なのは 楽しむ心
The important thing is a heart that enjoys
準備はいいかな 遅れないでね
Are you ready? Don't be late
手拍子子拍子一気に
Clap your hands together at once
靴紐結んで
Tie your shoelaces
お空まで飛び出せ
And fly out into the sky
ワクワクしたくない？
Don't you want to get excited?
ドキドキしたくない？
Don't you want to get heart-throbbing?
ウキウキさせてよ
Make me feel cheerful
もういいかい？
Are you ready?
まだまだ！
Not yet!
何故か止まらない
For some reason, I can't stop
何故か止まれない
For some reason, I can't be stopped
まだまだ
Not yet
明日の景色を見たくなくなーい
I don't want to see tomorrow's scenery yet
咲き誇れ！
Bloom in full glory!
夢色フェスティバル
Yumairo Festival
祭り囃子リズムで
With the rhythm of festival music
ノリノリ笑顔満開無限大
Excited smiles in full bloom, infinitely
舞い上がれ！
Soar high!
虹色に染め上げて
Dye it in rainbow colors
鏡に教えたい
I want to tell the mirror
これから
From now on
そんな感じで
Going like that
夢のヒート聴かせてよ
Let me hear the heat of your dreams
君色　教えて　color
Tell me your color
そんな感じで　イェイ　イェイ　イェイ　イェイ
Just like that, yeah yeah yeah yeah
夢のビート　刻もうよ
Let's carve out the beat of our dreams
さわげー！
Make some noise!
咲き誇れ！　ソレ　ソレ　ソレ　ソレ
Bloom in full glory! Heave-ho!
だから歌いたい　今のフェスティバル
That's why I want to sing at today's festival
祭り囃子で　ノリノリせい！
Get into the groove with the festival music!
笑顔満開　無限大
Smiles in full bloom, infinitely
It's Alright!
舞い上がれ！　ソレ　ソレ　ソレ　ソレ
Soar high! Heave-ho!
君色　教えて　color
Tell me your color
そんな感じで　イェイ　イェイ　イェイ　イェイ
Just like that, yeah yeah yeah yeah
夢のビート　響かせてよ
Let the beat of our dreams resonate
だから止まらない！
So I won't stop!
はっ！
Ha!
それ！　ソレ　ソレ　ソレ！
There! Heave-ho!
どっこいしょー！　どっこいしょー！
Dokkoisho! Dokkoisho!
まだ云わないで呪文めいたその言葉
Don't say those spell-like words just yet
“愛”なんて羽のように軽いささやき
Something like "love" is a whisper light as a feather
パパよりやさしく手なずけてあげるわ
I'll tame you more gently than a father would
覚悟があるならば
If you have the resolve
百万の薔薇のベッドに埋もれ眠る夢よりも
More than a dream of sleeping buried in a bed of a million roses
馨しく私は生きてるの
I am living fragrantly
汚れたこの世界　汚れずに
In this tainted world, without becoming tainted
羽ばたいていけるのか
Can one go on fluttering their wings?
ひとり真夜中
Alone in the middle of the night
学び続けても
Even if I continue to learn
水晶の星空は
The crystal starry sky
遠すぎるの
Is far too distant
まだ触れないでその震える指先は
Don't touch me yet, those trembling fingertips are
花盗人の甘いためらい
The sweet hesitation of a flower thief
触れてもいいこの深い胸の奥まで
You may touch, even to the depths of this heart
その自信があるならば
If you have that confidence
白馬の王子様なんて
Someone like a prince on a white horse
信じてるわけじゃない
It's not like I believe in that
ひび割れたガラスケースに飾られた純潔は
The purity displayed in a cracked glass case is
滅びゆく天使たちの心臓
The hearts of perishing angels
また明日も目覚めるたびに
Every time I wake up tomorrow as well
百年の時を知る
I realize the passage of a hundred years
眠れない魂の茨姫
The Briar Rose of a sleepless soul
食い込む冠
The crown digging in
一滴の血の滴
A single drop of blood
いま真真実と現実を思い知るの
Now I realize the truth and reality
まだ行かないで月明かりの結界で
Don't go yet, within the barrier of moonlight
過ちに気づいてしまいそう
I feel like I might realize my mistake
安らかな温もりだか...
This peaceful warmth...
ダンスの罪の
Is it a sin of dance
罰なのでしょうか
Or is it a punishment?
そっそっ零れてくる
Even the secret of the tears
涙の秘密さえ
That keep spilling out
わからない
I do not know
もう言わないで
Don't say it anymore
呪文めいたその言葉
That spell-like word
“愛”なんて
Called "love"
鎖のように重い
It's heavy like a chain
ささやいて
Whisper it
パパより優しく
Gentler than a father
手練のベッド
On a bed of skilled hands
どんな凄まじい
What a tremendous
デジャブならば
Deja vu it would be
さあ誓ってよ
Come, swear to me
その震える唇で
With those trembling lips
蜜を摘む
Pluck the nectar
狩人と化して
Turn into a hunter
ひそやかに
Secretly
この深い胸の奥底を
Deep into this chest
射る勇気が
If you have the courage
あるのならば
To shoot through
あなた捕まえたら
If I catch you
決して逃がさない
I'll never let you go
呼び覚まして
Awaken me
ぶつけたところから
From the place where we bumped
熟れていく果実のように
Like a ripening fruit
僕らは些細なことで
We, over small things
濁り合えたような かさぶたになれずに
Seemed to get muddied, unable to become a scab
息せき切ってがむしゃらに
Out of breath, frantically
輝く一等星を目指して
Aiming for a shining first-magnitude star
手を伸ばしたような
As if reaching out our hands
繊細されど大胆だ
Delicate yet bold
うるさいこれが真理だ
Shut up, this is the truth
泣き虫されど決断だ
A crybaby yet decisive
うるさいこれが本音だ
Shut up, this is the real feeling
未開拓冒険時代
Unexplored era of adventure
好奇心旺盛時代
Era of overflowing curiosity
何が綺麗かわかる？
Do you know what is beautiful?
昼間ならばある
If it's daytime, it's there
恥ずかしいか青春は
Is youth embarrassing?
馬鹿らしいか真剣は
Is being serious ridiculous?
僕ら全力でやってんだ
We're doing it with all our might
振りかざせ存在を
Brandish your existence
掻き乱せ心臓を
Stir up your heart
あとどれくらい 続いてくだろう
How much longer will it continue?
守り抜いた青春が
The youth we protected
何よりの贅沢だ
Is the greatest luxury
きっといつか 焦がれ思い返す
Surely someday I'll look back longingly
名前のない関係を
A relationship without a name
捨てきれない感情を
Emotions I can't throw away
何気ない今日を 忘れないでね
Don't forget this casual today
悩んでた種の色が
The color of the seed I worried over
昨日とはまるで違うとか
Is completely different from yesterday
そんな日常茶飯事で
With such daily occurrences
心は素直のようだ
The heart seems honest
戦友だとか親友は
Comrades or best friends
うるさいどれも正解だ
Shut up, they're all correct
初恋だとか失恋は
First love or heartbreak
うるさいどれも宝石だ
Shut up, they're all gems
天才的人生規格
Genius-like life plan
問題集対抗美学
Problem set opposition aesthetics
君は何してんのかな？
I wonder what you're doing?
話がしたい
I want to talk
風に乗って青春が
Youth riding on the wind
この思いを運んだ
Carried these feelings
僕ら全力を超えたいんだ
We want to exceed our full power
引き連れていこうぜ
Let's take them with us!
この上ない今日を過ごしたいよ
I want to spend this best day ever!
今しかできないことがある
There are things only possible now
今しかできない恋がある
There's a love only possible now
今しかできないから僕らに
Because it's only possible now, to us...
託された時間が惜しい
...the time entrusted is precious
今しか見られない君の笑顔も
Your smile that can only be seen now
君の涙も
Your tears too
君の全てでも
Even everything about you
大人びていく
You're growing up
有限だから最高だ
It's the best because it's finite
恥ずかしいが青春は
It's embarrassing, but youth is...
馬鹿らしいが真剣は
It's ridiculous, but being serious is...
僕ら全力でやってんだ
Something we're doing with all our might!
振りかざせ存在を
Brandish your existence
掻き乱せ心臓を
Stir up your heart
胸に刻めば続いてくだろう
If you engrave it in your chest, it will surely continue
守り抜いた青春が
The youth we've protected...
何よりもの贅沢だ
...is the greatest luxury of all
きっといつか焦がれ思い返す
Surely someday you'll yearn and look back
名前のない関係を
A relationship with no name
捨てきれない感情を
Feelings you can't throw away
何気ない今日を忘れないでね
Don't forget this casual day, okay?
この上ない今日を忘れないでね
Don't forget this best day ever, okay?
あー、アイドルだから！
Ah, because I'm an idol!
挑み続けるんだ
I'll keep challenging
君と夢見るんだ
I'll dream with you
不器用で悪いか
Is it wrong to be clumsy?
咲き誇るよ
I'm going to bloom!
咲き誇れアイドル
Bloom Proudly, Idol
初めてのイベント 準備なしで そんな私が夢を見ました
First event, without any preparation, I had a dream of myself like that
アイドルという生き方 憧れて
Longing for the way of life as an idol
無敵エリート 笑顔はチート
Invincible elite, my smile is a cheat
こんな私を見てくれる君
You who looks at me like this
好きなとこはどこですか？
What part of me do you like?
わがままは許して
Forgive my selfishness
ステージ経験値 涙に滲んで
Stage experience points blurred by tears
それでも絶対負けたくない
But I absolutely don't want to lose
桜にメッセージ乗せて届け！
Put a message on the cherry blossoms and let it reach!
愛であふれますように
May it be filled with love
あー、アイドルだから！
Ah, because I'm an idol!
挑み続けるんだ
I'll keep challenging
君と夢見るんだ
I'll dream with you
不器用で悪いか
Is it wrong to be clumsy?
咲き誇れ
Bloom!
本気だけどちょっと笑っちゃいな
I'm serious, but go ahead and laugh a little
私らしく桜色ね
In my own way, cherry blossom color, right?
ねー！
Hey!
磨いたスキル 実力発揮
Polished skills, showing my true ability
楽しめる日も増えてきたんだ
The days I can enjoy have increased
アイドルとして生きてる
Living as an idol
君のおかげ
Thanks to you
アホ毛もキュート 勝ち確ルート
Cowlick is also cute, a guaranteed victory route
そんな私についてきてよね！
Follow me like that, okay!
どじなとこも許されて
Being forgiven for my clumsy parts too
最強じゃん！
I'm the strongest!
痛いの痛いのグッと飲み込んで
Swallowing down all the pain
笑顔で笑顔増やしたいな
I want to increase smiles with a smile
桜前線が君の街に
The cherry blossom front to your town
春を届けるように
Like delivering spring
あー、アイドルだけは！
Ah, an idol only!
誇りたくないんだ
I don't want to be proud
君に見せたいんだ
I want to show you
理想を超えていくのよ
Surpassing ideals
駆け抜ける最高景色 見せてあげる
I'll show you the best scenery as I run through
信じていいよ
You can believe me
桜を咲かそう
Let's make the cherry blossoms bloom
みんなで咲かそう
Let's all make them bloom
満開のピンクで世界染めて
Dyeing the world in full bloom pink
あー、この涙はね
Ah, these tears, you know...
悲しい方じゃないから安心して
They aren't the sad kind, so rest assured
綺麗だね
They're beautiful, right?
今年も誕生日お祝いしてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for celebrating my birthday again this year!
みんな、大好きだよ！
Everyone, I love you all!
アイドルだから！
Because I'm an idol!
...アイドルだから
...Because I'm an idol.
挑み続けるんだ 君と夢見るんだ
I'll keep on challenging, dreaming with you.
不器用でいいか
Is it okay to be clumsy?
咲き誇れ もっと それだけじゃ終われない世界 私らしく
Bloom proudly, more. In a world that doesn't end with just that, in my own way.
さくら色ね♡
It's cherry blossom colored, isn't it? ♡
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
みんなー！ありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ありがとうねー！
ありがとう！
Thank you!
お祝いしてくれてありがとうねー！
Thank you for celebrating with me!
楽しんでるー？
Are you having fun?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
んー、まっ！
Mwah!
見てるよー！みんな見てるよー！
I'm watching! I'm watching everyone!
よし！ということでね、ライブまだまだ盛り上がる準備できてますかー！？
Alright! So, are you ready to get even more hyped for the live!?
みんなー！まだまだ見逃さないでね！
Everyone! Don't look away yet!
よし、次の曲いきます！
Alright, let's go to the next song!
Now I'm ready, I'm ready to go. 花が咲く時が来たんだ
Now I'm ready, I'm ready to go. The time for the flowers to bloom has come.
Are you ready? わかるでしょ
Are you ready? You know, right?
やってみせる Make it through
I'll show you I can do it, make it through.
ほらほら ソワソワ してたら
Look, look, if you're restless,
時は過ぎちゃうから 今すぐに Let's work it out
time will pass by, so let's work it out right now.
もう 目を背けやしないんだ
I won't look away anymore.
自分で Make it better 作る正解を
I'll make it better myself, creating the right answer.
I just wanna, just wanna find somebody
私よりも強気な誰か Oh
someone even more confident than me, oh.
夢中になる Make you hot 準備体操
Get absorbed, make you hot. Warm-up exercises,
隅々まで 刻んだ Victory So now start the war!
engraved into every corner. Victory. So now start the war!
I'm fighting my way, I'm fighting my way
夢の未来 信じて進むだけ
just moving forward, believing in the future of my dreams.
誰にも絶対 負ける気なんかない
I have absolutely no intention of losing to anyone!
君に見せたいの 彼方の景色を！
I want to show you the scenery beyond!
恋に踊れ 夢を注げ
Dance in love, pour in your dreams.
もっと突き進みたいの 止まらない
I want to push forward even more, I won't stop.
All ready fight Start of my life
最高潮へ今
To the climax now.
ちょっと待ってんか 紅い生娘 困っちゃうな
Wait a minute, the red maiden is troubled.
ねえ 今日こそ正々堂々 分け合えばいいの
Hey, today of all days, let's share fair and square.
Just wanna keep challenging myself
ほら こんなファンタジー 本望かな
Look, is this fantasy what I really want?
もっともっと欲しくなっちゃうよ
I'm starting to want more and more.
もう 何も 恐れはしないんだ
I'm not afraid of anything anymore.
君となら 勇気が湧くから Come join us
Because with you, courage wells up. Come join us.
ほら 今 聞こえて来るから
Look, I can hear it now.
私の名を呼ぶ Howl
The howl calling my name.
I'm fighting my way, I'm fighting my way
夢の未来 信じて進むだけ
just moving forward, believing in the future of my dreams.
誰にも絶対 負ける気なんかない
I have absolutely no intention of losing to anyone!
君に見せたいの 彼方の景色を！
I want to show you the scenery beyond!
運命任せ 夜を抜け
Leave it to fate, pass through the night.
大空彼方へ羽ばたけ
Flap your wings toward the distant sky.
一つも 無駄はないから
Since nothing is wasted,
力に変えて 動いてくから
I'll turn it into strength and keep moving.
昨日昨日 散々弾けた
Yesterday, yesterday, I had so much fun.
顔に 泥を 塗るなんて
I won't let anything bring me down.
運命手繰り寄せ Make you high
Pulling fate close, make you high.
後悔させはしないんだ 踊り出すのさ Start the war!
I won't let you regret it. I'll start dancing, start the war!
I'm fighting with myself, I'm fighting with myself
負けなんて無い 駆け抜けて行くだけ
There's no such thing as losing, just running through.
もう自分以外 私に勝てない
No one but myself can beat me.
君がいれば 何度も立ち上がるわ！
With you here, I'll stand up again and again!
愛を求めて 思い詰めて
Seeking love, thinking too much.
逃げたくはない 負けたくない 止まらない
I don't want to run away, I don't want to lose, I won't stop.
I need you today You make me feel so high
生かされてんだ いざ 空の上まで
I'm kept alive, now, to the top of the sky.
Ahhh
ooh
uh
唸るぜ
I'll roar!
血泥ついたって守りたい
I want to protect you even if I'm covered in blood and mud
革命道中だって君に夢中
Even in the middle of a revolution, I'm crazy about you
暗闇染み込む世界で見つけた
Found in a world soaked in darkness
センチメンタルな恋
A sentimental love
革命道中
Revolutionary Journey
甘く ぬかるんだ眼差し
A sweet, muddy gaze
変に 色気あるから困った
I'm in trouble because of your strange sexiness
手をつなぐ勇気出したくて
Wanting to find the courage to hold hands
身の程わきまえてちゃできないね
I can't do it if I know my place
暗いトンネルの壁 したたり落ちる飛沫
Droplets dripping down the walls of a dark tunnel
しめやかに 高鳴る心
Quietly, my heart is racing
ダメダメ
No, no
待て待て
Wait, wait
呪いも闇も抱きしめたい
I want to embrace both the curses and the darkness
心で暴れちゃってもいいかな
Is it okay if I run wild in my heart?
唸るぜ 血泥ついたって守りたい
I'll roar! I want to protect you even if I'm covered in blood and mud
革命道中だって君に夢中
Even in the middle of a revolution, I'm crazy about you
暗闇染み込む世界で見つけた
Found in a world soaked in darkness
センチメンタルな恋
A sentimental love
ダメダメ 待て待て
No, no, wait, wait
なりふり構わず側にいたい
I want to be by your side, no matter what
不器用な君にも期待しちゃうよ
I find myself expecting things from clumsy you
しがみつけば消えそうな君に
To you, who looks like you'll disappear if I cling to you
恋の爪立てて近づいてもいい？
Is it okay if I approach you with my claws of love?
身を任せたからって すべて失ってもいい
Even if I entrust myself and lose everything
しめやかに 高鳴る心
Quietly, my heart is racing
ダメダメ 待て待て
No, no, wait, wait
呪いも闇も君となら
The curses and the darkness, if it's with you
心で暴れちゃってもいいかな
Is it okay if I run wild in my heart?
荒れ狂え 絶句しちゃうまで離れない
Go wild, I won't let go until I'm breathless
革命道中だって君に夢中
Even in the middle of a revolution, I'm crazy about you
たゆたう旅の狭間で見つけた
Found in the intervals of a drifting journey
センチメンタルな恋
A sentimental love
突き進むなら二人で
If we're to push forward, it must be the two of us
革命道中だって夢に熱中
Even in the middle of a revolution, I'm absorbed in a dream
ダメダメ 待て待て
No, no, wait, wait
呪いも闇も抱きしめたい
I want to embrace both the curses and the darkness
心で暴れちゃってもいいよね
Is it okay if I run wild in my heart?
怖くて 唸るぜ 血泥ついたって守りたい
It's scary, I'll roar! I want to protect you even if I'm covered in blood and mud
革命道中だって君に夢中
Even in the middle of a revolution, I'm crazy about you
暗闇染み込む世界で見つけた
Found in a world soaked in darkness
センチメンタルな恋
A sentimental love
CHANGE
飛んで 飛んで
Fly, fly
奥底 願う味を
To the depths, the taste I wish for
一世一代 さよならだ
Once in a lifetime, it's goodbye
問答無用
No questions asked
勝ちか負けるか
Win or lose
ドロなんてないわ
There's no mud / It's not a draw
幕開けるわ
The curtain rises
Gimme the lucky money
どっちも無理 cigar cigar
Both are impossible, cigar cigar
引けるか残るか自分次第だな
Whether to pull or stay, it's up to me
余裕で 見切り全う ベットだ yeah yeah yeah
With ease, full decision, it's a bet, yeah yeah yeah
そこどけ そこ退け
Get out of the way, get out of the way
勝たせろ 後退りせん
Let me win, I won't back down
Stay gain better days
この船なら並みじゃない
This ship is anything but ordinary
Never again
Don't get in my way, jam it!
ちょっと待って
Wait a second
ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー
One two three, one two three, one two three
Sit down, Sit down
ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー
One two three, one two three, one two three
Hmm
はーもう フリーズ決まって 嫌投げんのは 些細草
Hah, enough with the freezing, throwing a fit is trivial
自家そんな小さい 差じゃ 量れないな
With such a small margin, you can't measure it
でしょう？ そりゃそう！ Say Good-bye あっかんべー
Right? Of course! Say Good-bye, *sticking tongue out*
あっちこっち そっちこっち なしなし ヤムヤム
Here and there, this way and that, nope nope, yum yum
未知なき道よ ヤムヤムヤム
An unknown path, yum yum yum
空回りそう でもまだ止めないで
Feels like I'm spinning my wheels, but don't stop yet
花回りそう 声越え オシャレ目に
Flowers spinning, surpassing voices, stylishly
Give us way
アンタはここまで 後ろだけ見とけ
This is as far as you go, just watch my back
はー ガチしてラッキーマネー どっちも無理 強が強が
Hah, getting serious for lucky money, neither is possible, bluffing bluffing
退けるか否か 自分次第だろ？
Whether you back down or not is up to you, right?
余裕で 吹っ切るぜ なんてったって Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah
I'll break through with ease, because after all, Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah
そこらの 底のエース かっさらうのは アタシらだ
The aces from the bottom around here, we're the ones who'll snatch them up
Stay もういい 勝ったなら平常心
Stay, that's enough, keep your cool if you've won
ねぇプレイボーイ行け Don't get in my way
Hey playboy, go, don't get in my way
ちょっと待って
Wait a second
ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー
One two three, one two three, one two three
Sit down, Sit down
ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー
One two three, one two three, one two three
まさかのバイバイ
An unexpected goodbye
ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー
One two three, one two three, one two three
Sit down, Sit down
ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー ワン ツー スリー
One two three, one two three, one two three
Sit down, Sit down
特報！
Special News!
フルアニメーションMV
Full Animation MV
配信後プレミア公開！
Premiering after the stream!
MV公開に先駆けてー
Leading up to the MV release...
ARE YOU READY?
ファッションビート
Fashion Beat
痛くて 目を塞いでも 聞こえちゃう 不況ショー
Even if it hurts and I close my eyes, I still hear the recession show
悩んでも変わらないから なんだかんだ やるしかないか
Worrying won't change anything, so one way or another, I just have to do it
壊れるならいっそ 直しやすいように
If it's going to break, let it be in a way that's easy to fix
どんな形 目指せるかな
I wonder what kind of shape I can aim for
助走なしのジャンプ 荷物なしでダイブ
A jump without a run-up, a dive without any baggage
今日のあたし 褒めてあげたいじゃんか
I want to praise the me of today, don't I?
息したい もっと 響きたい
I want to breathe, I want to resonate more
ねぇあたし以上が見れるかも 妄想止まんないや
Hey, maybe you'll see something beyond me, my delusions won't stop
ファッションビート 変えてみたい 夢に熱をなんて 吐きやしないな
Fashion Beat, I want to change it, I won't spout things like putting heat into dreams
叶えるのはあたし自身か それとも誰かにお任せか？
Will I be the one to make it come true, or will I leave it to someone else?
トントン 自分に勝ちたい
Knock knock, I want to win against myself
ニュー・ファッションビート 愛を配れ 負けるなんてごめんだ 味がしないな
New Fashion Beat, distribute love, I refuse to lose, it leaves a bad taste
何度でも灰になる進化 生まれ変わるたび新装開店
Evolution that turns to ash again and again, a grand reopening every time I'm reborn
まだ まだ 腐ってあげない 想定外
Not yet, I won't rot for you yet, it's unexpected
チクチク 削ってくるのは アキアキしてるわ
I'm sick and tired of those constant little stabs
ごめん 鬱陶しい言葉遊びは どうかちゃんとしまっておいて
Sorry, but please put away those annoying word games
私こそがライバル 当たり前の解釈 どうしたらいい わかってるのに
I am the rival, the natural interpretation, even though I know what I should do
助走なしのジャンプ 荷物なしでダイブ
A jump without a run-up, a dive without any baggage
今日のあたし 出来る気しないなって
Feeling like I can't do it today
気にしない なんて 無理じゃない？
To say 'I don't care', isn't that impossible?
ねぇあたし以外と比べても クソつまんないじゃんか
Hey, even if you compare me with others, it's so boring, isn't it?
ファッションビート 変えてみたい 夢に熱をなんて 吐きやしないな
Fashion Beat, I want to change it, I won't spout things like putting heat into dreams
叶えるのはあたし自身か それとも誰かにお任せか？
Will I be the one to make it come true, or will I leave it to someone else?
トントン 自分に勝ちたい
Knock knock, I want to win against myself
ニュー・ファッションビート 愛を配れ 負けるなんてごめんだ 味がしないな
New Fashion Beat, distribute love, I refuse to lose, it leaves a bad taste
何度でも灰になる進化 生まれ変わるたび新装開店 まだ...
Evolution that turns to ash again and again, a grand reopening every time I'm reborn, not yet...
まだ まだ 散ってあげない そんな
I'm not going to fade away just yet
止まれない
I can't stop
誰かじゃない 私自身だ
It's not someone else, it's me
生まれ変わる 負けの近況
Reborn from my recent losses
まだ まだ 散ってあげない そんな
I'm not going to fade away just yet
みんな ライブ 見てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for watching the live stream!
これからは 告知の時間です。
Now, it's time for some announcements.
まずは こちら！
First up, this!
さくらみこ 誕生記念 2026 記念グッズです！
Sakura Miko Birthday Celebration 2026 Commemorative Goods!
まず 1つ目、こちら！ デデーン！
First item, here it is! Ta-da!
アクリルパネル！
Acrylic Panel!
イラストレーターは おるだん先生に描き下ろしていただきました。
Illustrated by Ordan-sensei specifically for this.
テーマは 電脳世界の みこ！ 新衣装のみこを 描き下ろしてもらいました。
The theme is Cyber-World Miko! Featuring Miko in her new outfit.
オーロラ加工で キラキラのアクリルパネルとなっております。 めっちゃ可愛い！
It's a sparkling acrylic panel with an aurora finish. It's so cute!
続いては こちら。 スマホスタンドフィギュアです！
Next up is this: a smartphone stand figure!
スマホが立てかけられる スタンド。 そして新衣装の みこのフィギュア。
A stand where you can prop up your phone, featuring a figure of Miko in her new outfit.
めちゃくちゃ可愛くないですか？ これ たくさんね、こだわったので...
Isn't it super cute? I put a lot of work into the details...
ぜひね、このスタンドに スマホを立てかけて 配信見てくれたら 嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you prop your phone on this stand to watch my streams!
続いては こちら！
Moving on to the next one!
ガジェットケース！
Gadget Case!
新衣装にちなんで、こういう あまり出さないグッズも 考えてみました。
Since it's for the new outfit, I thought of some unique goods we don't usually release.
ケーブルとかね、モバイルバッテリーなど 小物を収納できるケースとなっております。
It's a case for storing small items like cables and mobile batteries.
ソフトな素材になってるよ！
It's made of a soft material!
最後は こちら！
And finally, this!
ナイロンジャケット！
Nylon Jacket!
新衣装を モチーフにした ナイロンジャケットとなっております。
This nylon jacket is designed with the motif of the new outfit.
ちょっとカッコイイめの デザインなので、みんな 一緒にお揃いになってくれたら 嬉しいです！
It has a slightly cool design, so I'd be happy if everyone wore matching ones!
そして、フルセット購入特典は こちら！
And here is the bonus for purchasing the full set!
さくらみこ 直筆サイン ＆ 箔押し複製メッセージ入り おるだん描き下ろし ポストカードとなっております。
A postcard illustrated by Ordan, featuring my handwritten signature and a foil-stamped message.
数量限定には なるんですが、みんな お早めに よろしくお願いします！
It's available in limited quantities, so please grab yours early!
通常版は、さくらみこ 箔押し複製サイン ＆ メッセージ入りの ポストカードとなっております。
The regular version comes with a postcard featuring a foil-stamped signature and message.
みんな ぜひね、たくさん 手に入れてくれると 嬉しいです！ よろしくお願いします！
I'd be so happy if many of you could get one! Thank you!
そして 告知 2つ目は こちら！
And for the second announcement, this!
なんと、さくらみこ × 学研さんの 参考書シリーズが 発売決定になりました！
To my surprise, a Sakura Miko x Gakken study book series will be released!
ホロライブ スタディブック 『さくらみこでもわかる』シリーズ となっております。
It's the Hololive Study Book "Miko Can Understand It Too" series.
中学漢字＋語彙、中学数学、中学英単語、中学地理＋都道府県の 4冊が 発売決定です！
Four books: Junior High Kanji & Vocabulary, Math, English, and Geography & Prefectures.
初回限定の 愛蔵版も 発売予定となっております。
A first-edition limited collector's version is also planned for release.
4月下旬頃より 予約開始なので、引き続き 続報チェックしてね！
Reservations start around late April, so keep an eye out for updates!
『みこでもわかる』シリーズ、みんな 説得力が あると思うよね？
The "Miko Can Understand" series... everyone thinks that's convincing, right?
次！ 3つ目は こちら！
Next! The third one is this!
さくらみこ × フレーベル館、初の絵本 『みこぴーと おおきな さくらのき』が 本日より 発売です！
Sakura Miko x Froebel-kan, my first picture book "Mikopi and the Big Cherry Tree" is on sale starting today!
もう 買ってくれた人も いるかな？
Has anyone bought it already?
いつも支えてくれている みこぴーを題材に、夢だった絵本を 作ることができました！
Using the Mikopis who always support me as a theme, I was able to create my dream picture book!
全国の書店や ローソンさんで購入可能なので、ぜひぜひ みんな 手に取ってください！
It's available at bookstores nationwide and at Lawson, so please go pick up a copy!
頑張りました！
I worked really hard on it!
続いては こちら 大発表！ 4つ目は こちら！
And now for a major announcement! The fourth one is this!
さくらみこ フィギュア化が 決定しました！
A Sakura Miko figure release has been confirmed!
おるだん先生 監修にて、みこの夢だった 等身大フィギュアが ついに 完成です！ やったー！
Supervised by Ordan-sensei, my dream life-size figure is finally finished! Yay!
スケールフィギュアも 同時に 予約販売が 決まりました。
Pre-orders for the scale figure have also been confirmed for release at the same time.
明日 3月 6日から 予約開始です！
Reservations start tomorrow, March 6th!
エキスポの デザインココさんブースで 展示されるので、みんな 見に来てね！ たくさん写真撮ってね！
It'll be on display at the Design COCO booth at the Expo, so come see it! Take lots of photos!
また、この 等身大フィギュアも 展示される、
Also, where this life-size figure will be exhibited...
京都 IP書店 オープン記念 × さくらみこの ポップアップショップも 開催決定となりました！ すごい！
The Kyoto IP Bookstore Grand Opening x Sakura Miko Pop-up Shop is also confirmed! Amazing!
リニューアルオープンした 京都 蔦屋 IP書店さんで 4月 28日から 開催です！
It will be held at the newly reopened Kyoto Tsutaya IP Bookstore starting April 28th!
オリジナルグッズの 発売や、ノベルティの コラボも 行われるので、みなさん 楽しみにしていてください！
There will be original goods for sale and collaboration novelties, so look forward to it, everyone!
盛りだくさんだー！
There's so much going on!
そして まだ ございます！ 続いては こちら！
And there's still more! Next up is this!
HYTE × さくらみこ コラボPCケース 発売決定！
HYTE x Sakura Miko Collaboration PC Case release confirmed!
キーキャップとデスクマットのセットもございます。
A set of keycaps and a desk mat is also available.
先行予約開始のメール通知や詳細については、
For pre-order email notifications and details,
hyte.co/miko を見てみてね。
please check out hyte.co/miko.
楽しみにしててね！
Please look forward to it!
そして今年も、さくらみこ×鳴門鯛焼本舗さんのコラボが実施中デス！
And this year too, the Sakura Miko x Naruto Taiyaki Honpo collaboration is ongoing!
今年でなんと4回目です！ありがとうございます。
It's actually the 4th time this year! Thank you so much.
3月31日までなので、みんなぜひ食べに行ってみてね！
It's until March 31st, so everyone, please go and try some!
続いて、新曲「ファッションビート」本日0時よりリリースです！
Next, the new song 'Fashion Beat' will be released at midnight today!
MVはこのあとプレミア公開！みんな見てね！
The MV will have a premiere after this! Everyone, watch it!
とっても豪華なアニメMVとなっております。よろしくお願いします。
It's a very luxurious anime MV. Please check it out.
はい！そしてこちら！明日からホロライブエキスポと7thフェス開催です！
Yes! And this! Hololive EXPO and the 7th Fes start tomorrow!
3日間の開催ですよ、すごい！
It's a three-day event, wow!
みこはですね、7thフェスではDay 2のStage 2に参加します。みんな見に来てね！
As for Miko, I'll be participating in Stage 2 on Day 2 of the 7th Fes. Come see me!
このあとはメンバー限定の撮影会もあるので、みんなみこぴーになってね！
There's a member-only photo session after this, so everyone, become a Mikopi!
ということで告知がモリモリのモリになりましたが、みんなついてこれたかな？
So, there were a ton of announcements, but did everyone keep up?
みここれからも頑張るので、よろしくお願いします。
Miko will keep doing her best, so please support me.
誕生日祝ってくれてありがとう！
Thanks for celebrating my birthday!
おつみこー！
Otsumiko!
出演：さくらみこ
Cast: Sakura Miko
戌神ころね、百鬼あやめ
Inugami Korone, Nakiri Ayame
白上フブキ、大空スバル
Shirakami Fubuki, Oozora Subaru
大神ミオ、宝鐘マリン
Ookami Mio, Houshou Marine
常闇トワ、星街すいせい
Tokoyami Towa, Hoshimachi Suisei
映像制作 [OP映像] 紺屋本譜(スタジオメイビー)
Video Production [OP Video] Konyahonpo (Studio Maybe)
ポン酢(スタジオメイビー)、Kanauru
Ponzu (Studio Maybe), Kanauru
さくらみこ 誕生日記念2026
Sakura Miko Birthday Celebration 2026
アクリルパズル
Acrylic Puzzle
スマススタンドフィギュア
Smart Stand Figure
ガジェットケース
Gadget Case
ナイロンジャケット
Nylon Jacket
誕生日記念フルセット：直筆サイン入りメッセージ付き
Birthday Celebration Full Set: With hand-signed message
受注期間：2026年3/5(木)〜4/6(月) 18:00まで
Order Period: Mar 5 (Thu) - Apr 6 (Mon) 18:00, 2026